RALPH CADELIÑA

WEB DEVELOPER

WEBSITE: https://ralphcadelina.vercel.app/

CAREER **OBJECTIVE**

With a bachelor's degree holder in Information Technology with experience in the IT Industry particularly in Web Development. I venture in securing a position in a company where I can apply my experience that would best fit my qualifications. I aim to further enhance my values toward any responsibility that I will undertake.

SOFTWARE **DEVELOPMENT SKILLS**

- · HTML5, CSS, BOOTSTRAP, TAILWINDCSS
- · JAVASCRIPT, REACTJS
- MATERIAL UI, CHAKRA UI
- NODE JS
- FIREBASE
- API INTEGRATION (REST API)
- · PHP, LARAVEL, MYSQL

SERVER **ADMINISTRATION** SKILLS

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Surigao Education Center | 2012 - 2021

WORK EXPERIENCE

JR. FRONTEND DEVELOPER KRE8TIB I.T. SERVICES | AUG 2022 - OCT 2022

• Build and implements static web pages and email templates

SITE

SURIGAO EDUCATION CENTER | ADMINISTRATOR NOV. 2021 - MAY 2022

- Manage the official domain of the institution.
- Build the website from template through wordpress.
- Arrange the content and information of the institution.

TRAINING

- SERVERS (WINDOWS SERVER 2008/2012) FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP
- MICROSOFT OFFICE (365, WORD, EXCEL, Kodego | November 2022 March 2023 POWERPOINT, ACCESS & OUTLOOK)
- DATABASE MANAGEMENT (MYSQL)
- COMPUTER HARDWARE & SOFTWARE (INSTALL, REPAIR, TROUBLESHOOT, SALES & MAINTENANCE)

+639705368194 Email: ralphcadelina5@gmail.com